technogiants.net 2019-04-09

# TechnoGiants: Privacy Policy of Weblog

Supposing you require any additional information or will have any queries about our privacy policy, you are welcome to get in touch with us by sending an **Email** at [vaibhav@technogiants.net](mailto:vaibhav@technogiants.net)

At TechnoGiants, the privacy of our respective visitors is utmost importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and picked up by TechnoGiants and in what way it can be used.

 **Log Files**

Like all other Internet sites, TechnoGiants requires log files. The data contained in the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, kinds of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and wide range of clicks to evaluate trends, administer the blog, track user’s movement throughout the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, along with other such information won’t be linked with any information that is actually personally identifiable.

 **External Links**

TechnoGiants would likely have used external links specifically for your further references. However when you will have used these links to leave our blog, you need to understand that TechnoGiants do not possess any control over that site and never responsible for protection and privacy of those sites. Those sites are not governed by this privacy policy. If you locate any inaccurate or broken links, you can most welcome to contact me.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

TechnoGiants does use cookies to store information regarding visitor’s preferences, record user-specific details on which pages the reader access or visit, customize Web-page content based on visitor’s browser type or any additional information that the visitor sends via their browser.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information whenever you visit our web site. These companies possibly use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, both time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) throughout your visits to this as well as other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services very likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit this [PAGE](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a 3rd party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TechnoGiants. Google’s utilizing the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your current users dependent on their visit to the pages of our web-site as well as other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the utilization of the DART cookie by checking the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following [URL](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

It is more advisable you consult the respective privacy policies of such third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices and also for instructions about how exactly to opt-out of certain practices. TechnoGiants privacy policy doesn’t relate to, therefore we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or internet sites.

If you would like to disable cookies, you may do so at your individual browser options. More detailed information regarding cookie management with specific web browsers can be located at the browsers’ respective websites.

TechnoGiants has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
